The Pastry of Knowledge.
Tales have been told of this pastry as one
of the Seven Wonders of Eden College.
A mysterious pâtissier appears
out of nowhere at their cafeteria
and serves this pastry on a whim.
Not only is it exquisitely delicious,
but many students who taste these
pastries end up as Imperial Scholars.
So people started to say that eating
them will instantly make you smarter.
This caused some Eden students
to do everything they could for a
chance to order these pastries.
The Pastry of Knowledge
Oh, my! Could you be the
prince I met before?
No, I am but your clone.
No, I'm absolutely sure of it!
Those eyes! That hair!
Ah, my sweet prince! I love you!
No, I am but a female sheep like yourself.
Oh, dang it! We're not getting any
further in this story! It's all a mess!
I mean, these look exactly the same.
You can ignore that part
for the sake of the story!
Next is Anya's turn. It'll be a battle
story with twins separated at birth.
No! If we do anything with a battle,
they'll get all torn up.
Shock.
By the way, did you hear?
Next term, we're going to be
split up depending on our grades.
What's that mean?
It means...
The Smart Class
The Okay Class
There's me, who's okay at school...
And then there's you,
who's terrible at school.
The Needs Effort Class
Below That
Depending on how our lessons go,
we could be separated.
Shock!
Anya will be all alone!
You will! That's why you have to
work harder on your studies.
On top of our midterms and finals,
I hear our quiz tomorrow will
also be a determining factor.
So will our test on ancient language.
Ugh, this is bad.
It's all over for Anya.
Th-Th-Th-This is huge!
It happened! It appeared!
What? What happened?
It appeared in the second
cafeteria! That dessert!
Huh? What're you talking about?
You moron! You don't know?
The dessert made by the legendary
pâtissier who used to be a royal chef!
It's known as the Pastry of Knowledge!
The legendary dessert that's said
to make everyone who eats it
an Imperial Scholar!
Apparently, they're macarons this year.
There's only a limited amount, so we
gotta get them before someone else does!
O-Okay!
If I eat that, I'll be a genius, too!
* Please don't run in the hallway
I mean, I'm sure it's just a silly rumor,
but superstitions like
this can be important, too!
Besides, macarons made by a royal chef?
I'd want to eat them just for that!
They sound delicious!
What's a macaron?
Oh, that must be it! We need
to hurry, or they'll run out!
Gah!
Second Son.
Shrimp!
What are you in such a hurry for?
Shut up! Right back at you!
There's only one order left of
Pierre Pommier's new sweets.
First come first served!
You guys aren't going to get it!
This battle is basically over Stellas!
I'd like this, please.
You got it.
That's the last order of these for the day!
Wow, I got super lucky.
I wonder if I can get a Stella now.
I'm so excited.
George...
Huh?
Damn it! That's mine!
Hand those over! I was
supposed to eat those!
Wah! I'm being mugged!
I bought these with what little
money I have! You can't have them!
That's right! You never
gave me back my pen case!
Huh?
And you embarrassed me by making
me sing when I didn't need to.
That leaf will be avenged.
O-Okay, fine.
There are five of these,
so you can have the other four.
Then we'll be even.
Hey, you're a good guy.
Four left...
And so,
an epic battle to decide who would
become Imperial Scholars began.
We're gonna play a round of Old Maid.
The one who comes in last
doesn't get a macaron.
Okay, bring it on!
Anya's never played cards before
and doesn't know the rules.
Are you serious?
It's simple. You just need to match
the same numbers and avoid the joker.
Okee.
Fight!
Hey, give me the joker. We'll make
her take it and show her who's boss!
Roger!
The Pastry of Knowledge
would be wasted on
someone who doesn't even
know what Old Maid is.
Hey, it's your turn.
Anya has... a six, a four, a ten...
You don't need to tell them, Anya.
What a fool!
I'll make the joker easier to grab
and move the six farther
away so she won't grab it.
Go on. Pick one.
Six!
Huh?!
That was amazing, Anya!
Th-That was just dumb luck.
Four!
Ten!
A!
Some old guy!
Yay! Anya doesn't have any more cards!
Now, hang on! You're way too good!
Yeah! You obviously cheated!
You must've marked the cards or something!
Whatever! Stop being bad sports!
If she didn't cheat, the only answer
is that she can read minds!
Oh, no! I went too far!
If you insist, we can play again.
What? You're going too easy on them, Anya!
We're starting all over again
with a new set of cards!
We're changing our order, too!
And don't you dare cheat again!
I didn't.
That was close...
I need to mess up on purpose so they don't
find out about my telepath powers.
Ooh, I got the joker.
Here you go.
The joker's in the middle. Now, grab it!
I need to mess up on purpose...
Oh noes.
Anya has clumsily grabbed Mister Joker.
How lame!
You dumb moron!
Now it's time for my killer...
No, Anya. You can't hit him!
Luck's not on my side.
That was close. If I got expelled,
the mission would've been over.
I need to be a cool liar like Papa!
No problem.
Anya will be safe if the second
son grabs the Mister Joker next.
Take one.
Shock!
She's so incredibly obvious.
Welp, there's a pair.
Could it be that Second
Son can read minds, too?!
And I'm done!
Me, too!
Oh, no. I can't get rid of Mr. Joker.
I'm done, too!
You're pretty bad at this, too, Damian.
Shut up!
You've got this, Anya!
Here I go.
This will decide everything.
No, if I just watch her face,
I've got this in the bag!
I need to do my best lying face
so he'll grab Mister Joker!
If I lose, I won't be able to eat
that dessert and I'll stay dumb!
Then I'll do bad on my tests and be
in different classes than Becky!
Anya will be all alone!
Okay, this one must be the
one that's not the joker.
Okay, here you go, you four.
Yay! It looks so yummy!
So exciting.
Lord Damian, how could you
possibly pick the joker there?
Shut up!
She's so unfair... Damn it.
Second Son.
Want to split it with me?
N-N-N-N-No, I don't, you dummy!
I can become an Imperial Scholar
even if I don't eat that!
You eat it because you're stupid, stupid!
Grr.
My, how rude! Let's just eat them now, Anya.
Let's eat!
Yum!
Now I'll be able to get a Stella, too.
Now, begin your quiz.
Confirmed: Anya is going to be all alone.
The rest of my school life
is going to be dark.
Th-That's not true.
Let's do our best on the finals.
Yeah. You're still better off
than me, since I'm already a loner.
School tests are so difficult.
Anya is going to go sulk in bed for a bit.
Her basic academics have improved a little,
but she's still got a ways to go.
This test on ancient language...
She was docked points for
constant spelling errors,
but without that, she would've
gotten quite the score.
She hasn't studied ancient
language that much yet.
Did she learn it wherever she grew up?
But there aren't really any countries
that still use this ancient language.
No... There's no point in
wondering about this anymore.
Hey, Anya. I made you
Hamburg steak for dinner.
Hamburg steak!
And I tried making some dessert!
Bworf?!
Here's a fake ID to get into
Doust Industries' 2nd Section.
Here are the test numbers for the
engine test on their new fighter jet.
The Informant's Great Romance Plan II
Thanks, as always.
That's not for free.
What about the visual data on
the members of that one group?
Oh, yeah. About that...
You'll have to wait a bit more.
One of my contacts who knew
a lot about them was offed.
The State Security Service?
Nah. I'm not positive, but there
are rumors that Garden got him.
Garden?
The group of assassins who have
been in this country for ages?
They're basically urban legends, aren't they?
Nah, they definitely exist.
They eliminate one traitor after another
on the shadow government's orders.
I mean... I'm sure there's at
least one authorized militia here.
You dumbass! They're way
more serious than that!
Just one of their soldiers
can take down a whole squad!
Don't be ridiculous. I'm counting on you.
Wait! Help me out with one of my jobs
in exchange for this extra labor.
Job?
This guy.
LOST CAT
A lost cat?
This is Kopi. He belongs to a girl named Kacey,
who works at a café where I'm a regular.
He went missing last week,
and Kacey was super sad.
Twilight...
So that Kacey can smile again—
and while we're at it, so that
Kacey and I can get closer—
help me get this cat back.
Hey!
Hey, wait!
If you don't help me, I won't
give you any more information!
Hello?!
I'll even throw in this brand-new
pistol shaped like a toothbrush!
Damn it! He's such a heartless jerk!
Fine, then! I'll get the cat back on my own!
Don't go underestimating
an informant, damn it!
Hello? Jeffrey?
That's right. I've got a job for you.
I'm looking for a cat.
He's a male Nortblue, and he's
got a bell around his neck.
Let me know if you find him. Thanks.
It's been a while, Hound Joe.
You're the best guy I know for this job.
Heya, Terrance?
Yup, this is an emergency.
Hey, Nancy. You know a lot
about cats, don't you?
I'd like to talk to Harrison
at the 22nd Branch Office.
Hello, Mister Jasper.
Yo, Pat!
I saw a cat matching that description
on Ritter Street near city hall.
Excellent work, Joe.
He should be around here somewhere...
Oh? Franky?
Yor?
Hello.
Hey...
Oh, yeah, you work at city hall, don't you?
Yes. I'm about to take my lunch break.
Do you work near here as well, Franky?
Er, no. Actually...
There's a missing kitty?! Oh, my goodness!
I'd love to help you.
Huh? Uh, but you're about
to have lunch, aren't you?
Oh, don't worry!
My s-spouse... er, husband's
friend is in need, after all!
She's still keeping this husband
and wife act up all the time.
A-As long as I won't cause you any trouble...
In that case... Sure.
Of course!
So where is Mister Kopi?
We know for a fact that
he's around here somewhere.
I've placed several of my cat-shaped
wiretaps, C20s, at various cat spots.
They have a sensor that's supposed to react
to the sound of the bell around Kopi's neck.
That's amazing, Franky!
Yeah, I'm awesome.
The C20 at Point A is being attacked?!
Oh, no!
It got destroyed!
How about the other points?
I guess they were eliminated
for being outsiders.
So much for that plan.
I guess the world of kitties is also cruel.
Then we'll just have to have him come to us!
Time for the CAT-N.I.P decoy system!
Ooh!
We're gonna get the target to come to
us by spreading the smell of catnip!
Wow, you're just so talented, Franky!
Are you a craftsman?
Huh? I'm just a young man who
dreams of making the world
a better place with the inventions I create,
and also getting rich off of patents.
My, that's lovely!
I can't tell her that I actually
do pretty shady work.
Oh, dear...
Oh, shit! Too many of them showed up!
Which one is Mister Kopi?!
There! The gray one!
Huh? Huh?! Which one is he?!
Damn it! I'm gonna catch you, no matter what!
Please help me!
Hyper Long Hand! Take this!
Damn it, this isn't gonna work!
I need to be more direct!
Hey, get outta there!
My camera-shaped net launcher!
Kopi is definitely on his guard.
I'll have to carefully approach him
like I'm just gonna take a picture...
But because I made this
launcher look like a camera,
the range on it is super short.
I need to get within two meters
to make sure it catches him!
Come back here, damn it!
Oh, that must be Mister Kopi!
Oh, Kopi. Now you've made me mad.
It's too late to regret your actions now!
This is the ultimate weapon
that I spent ten years developing!
This should give me
superhuman powers! Allegedly.
The Exo-Skeleton Power Suit!
Just you wait! After I turn it on,
it takes 15 minutes for the
motor to get warmed up!
Just stay right there until then!
Hey! You dummy! That's a major
street over there! It's dangerous!
Stop! I'm sorry! I won't
chase you around anymore!
Franky, I'm going to borrow this for a sec...
Hi-yah!
I caught him!
I caught him, Franky!
U-Uh... Thanks.
Ten years... Ten years of my life...
Isn't this wonderful, Mister Kopi?
You get to go home now!
But then again...
It's a small price to pay if it
gets Kacey to look my way.
Wait for me, my honey!
USUAL CAFÉ
Oh, thank you, Franky!
Oh, Kopi! I was just so worried!
That's great, babe.
Darn it, Mark! This wouldn't have happened
if you hadn't left the front door open!
Look, I'm sorry.
I'll buy those matching
rings you've been wanting.
Uh, yeah. This is great, yup.
Well, I'll be going now.
Seriously, thank you so much, Franky!
Well... Live happily ever after, you two.
That man decided to live for his job.
Helping others always feels so wonderful.
You seem happy, Yor.
Ooh, why's that? Did your
hubby buy you something?
Huh? Oh, no.
Congrats on your happy marriage or whatever.
God, you piss me off.
She just finally learned how
to be normal, that's all.
Normal...
Am I normal?!
Huh?
Oh, thank goodness!
I'm glad I can pull off this act.
Hey, Sharon. Don't let her get too cocky.
Er... I meant that as sarcasm.
Hey, Briar.
Or rather, Forger. You've got a phone call.
Yes, sir! I am indeed Forger!
It's from your usual client.
Hello, this is Yor.
Hello.
You've got a customer, Thorn Princess.
The bright crimson that
appears right before my eyes
Stretches approximately 40,000 kilometers
Our wounds that inch closer behind us
Make us wander even more
when we're already lost
The unseeable, scentless, unmistakable future
Stabbed me in the back!
So...
Let me stay by your side tonight
Just for tonight, I'm going to be serious
Come closer to me
Even the future we prayed for
Has a different path
My dear
Our malice for each other
Might just get to us
Or maybe not
Plan to Cross the Border